The forecast for the end of according to what
I read was the morning of heat and
heat and heat because on top of that tomorrow
it was supposed to rain but it read
36 degrees so tomorrow In addition to the fact that the
heat is going to [ __ ] you the humidity is going
to  hit a rape and the mosquitoes are going to start
coming out because I have sung
that when it is humid the
mosquitoes come out they are going to [ __ ] on you eating the
mosquitoes [ __ ] summer the truth
is [ __ ] I don't know who the [ __ ]
likes this the guy who likes it  This is
because he likes to have a hard time because he has
a shitty life because he probably doesn't
want to go back home because his
family must hate him Because in
normal terms no one can ever
like having 35 degrees in the
center of the sunrise at this time no one
No one can like it, no one I'm already
sweating, I'm all stuck I want to
grab the steering wheel, all the plastic is sticking to me,
this one on the steering wheel, this
shitty one that gathers heat even in the
mirror, even Poronga, there's a son of a
[ __ ] who came in six years ago.  months at
work and they already gave him a flat with air
conditioning it seems that I must fall
like hell
walking around in this twisted [ __ ] that gathers
more heat than idiotic mercury I want
to die